而是因为我是黑人
They attack me 'cause I'm black.
我们遭受攻击的原因都一样
They attacked all of us for the same reason.
这位敌人严厉斥责我们
All of us catch hell from the same enemy.
- 我们的问题都一样...  - 问题都一样
- We're all in the same bag... - In the same bag.
- ...面临同样困境  - 面临同样困境
- In the same boat. - In the same boat.
- 我们遭受政治迫害...  - 我们遭受政治压害
-We suffer from political persecution... -We suffer from political persecution
- ...经济剥削...  - 经济剥削
- Economic exploitation... - Economic exploitation.
- ...社会地位低落  - 社会地位低落
- And social degradation. - And social degradation.
- 肇因于同一位敌人  - 肇因于同一位敌人
- All of 'em from the same enemy. - All of 'em from the same enemy.
- 政府让我们失望  - 政府让我们失望
- The government has failed us. - The government has failed us.
- 你无法否认  - 你无法否认
- You can't deny that. - You can't deny that.
生活在20世纪的1964年
Any time you're living in the 20th century, 1964,
在街道上唱着《我们一定赢》
and you walking around here singing "we shall overcome,"